We are in the midst, of course, of the NCAAs, and I'm happy to say that it's women's college
basketball that has really been the marquee events for the NCAAs. We're looking at Kaitlyn
Clark, and so is Ice Cube, founder of the Big Three. He is offering $5 million to Iowa Hawkeyes
basketball star Kaitlyn Clark. Lots of people are asking, why isn't that same offer going to
Angel Reese? And I think it really speaks to this idea that the Big Three is a commercial venture
and that he really does believe that he needs the white eyeballs in order for it to be successful.
It's kind of like the Eminem effect. If I get this other audience that might not have been tuned into
what I was doing already, maybe they'll stick around, but I do think Angel Reese will probably
be a bigger star than Kaitlyn Clark in the long run. Absolutely. I mean, Angel is a star. I would
love for Ice Cube to feel like I don't need to go and seek out middle America's approval because I
know that Black folks are going to pour into this space as long as I am pouring into Black folks.
I agree with you, but I think when they start seeing those numbers, the capitalistic mindset
just takes over and forgets all about this being a space that I created intentionally for a Black space.
You know, there's two kind of roads for this. Like in some cases, it's the capitalism that takes you
out of that. And in some cases, it's the lack of support that takes you out of that and ends up
pushing you into, well, let me just focus on the capitalism.